Guide to the Custodial and Administrative Services, Yale University, Photographs
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Custodial and administrative services, Yale University, photographs
1865-1959
RU 763
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
0.25
Photographs of Yale custodians and dining hall employees, some posed formally, some capturing work activities.
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 5-F (YRG 5-F), Records documenting operations and administrative services at Yale University.
Arrangement
Arranged by topic.
Scope and Contents
Photographs of Yale custodians and dining hall employees, some posed formally, some capturing work activities.
Food service employees; Universities and colleges -- Food service; Photographs; Yale University -- Employees
- Photographs, Series I
  - Grounds maintenance
    - Pruning, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Shoveling snow, Circa 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Physical plant
    - Bricklayers, Circa 1936-1937 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Painting, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - College carpenters [Charles McLinn], Circa 1886 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Dining halls
    - College dining halls, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Staff, 1953, n.d (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Commons, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Custodians ("Sweeps")
    - Group shot: S. & F. Allston, Jackson,Livingstone, Circa 1879 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified group shots, Circa 1875 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Smith and Jackson, Circa 1865 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Jackson, Circa 1875 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - William Cummings, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Baty, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - "Andrew the Janitor", Circa 1895 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Allston, Circa 1880s (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Unidentified individuals, Circa 1890 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Unidentified individual, Circa 1862 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Custodial laundry: Commons Laundry, Circa 1953 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Support services: Clerical Bureau, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Utility services: telephone exchange operators, 1955 June (Box 1, Folder 21)